Hello friends, welcome to this
video. Whenever you insure your bike through PhonePe,
you would see KYC pending there. So
how will you complete the KYC pending process?
For this, you will go to the history of PhonePe.
After coming to the history, to
see the insurance premium pad, you will
touch it once. Here you will see
KYC pending and then touch view policy once.
After touching it,
you will get to see all the details here.
Just below the pending KYC, you will see complete
KYC. You will touch it once.
After touching it, it will be a little long and you will
wait for it to load. Now
look here, you have to type the PAN number. You have to type the
PAN number of the person in whose name the vehicle is registered. You have to type it and
you will also have to type the date of birth
here. After typing, your date of birth
and name will be shown here. After all the data matches,
you will see the OK button here. You will
touch it on the right. It is the
submit button and
touch it once.  After doing this, there will be a little
process, we will wait a little till the process is done,
whatever data is found in the insurance server,
you will see eKYC in progress here, you
can see it on other, wait a little for one to two minutes here,
we will refresh once
or wait for one to two minutes, then
your insurance policy here will be
activated and the date will also be
advanced here and
you will get to see its PDF copy on the email ID you have given
and you can print the PDF copy from the mail, it has been
activated here
and you will also see the policy certificate number
and here your date has also been advanced
and you have to see it active here, so
whenever you have
pending eKYC,
you can do eKYC in this way from phone, and after doing it,
you will download the policy which you would have received on mail, and whatever
status you see here, see here
you will get to see that the policy has been successfully done.